so I'm living in Seattle now and I love
it it's my favorite place uh it's very
expensive to live so I have to have a
roommate which I've mentioned several
times before what I didn't mention to
you guys is my roommate is a lady and I
don't feel like a lot of y'all were
picturing a lady there and that's your
own bigotry that's between you and
yourself that's really something you
need to ask yourself
about we're not dating in any way she's
just my roommate just a friend of mine
uh she really the only person that can
tolerate me is what we say uh it's cool
it's weird there one of those girls she
like go out on days bring guys home I
don't know how to feel about that right
like she went to a bar the other day she
picked up a dude that guy came back to
our house stayed the night and then the
next morning all three of us found
ourselves eating breakfast
together and I'm going to tell you right
now Provo that guy had no idea what was
going
[Laughter]
on he was a little concerned
over what was going on there so I think
I'm Charming I like lighten the mood I
look at the guy I'm like come on man
we're both adults are we seriously going
to sit here eating eggs and not talk
about the fact that you slept with my
wife in our house last
[Laughter]
[Applause]
night and I just threw my eggs at the
wall and walked out out of the room you
know what I
[Music]
mean on my way out I whispered at her
though I was like hey good
luck oh yeah and the best thing is I can
do it again to any guy she brings over
what's she going to do warn him I don't
think that's going to
work what could she possibly say she's
going to like want to hear the rest of
the joke click the play button to
continue
watching